Dâmocles Gil Marçal

Senior Front-end Engineer

EXPERIENCE

Senior Front-end Engineer

Calculato

Nov 2019 - Present - 4 years 12 mos, Brazil

I Worked in the development team as Lead Front-end in web projects. I use all my software architecture knowledge to improve performance, maintainability, scalability and readability. I also use my development skills with the best customer experience in mind, with disruptive and value generating solutions.

Front-end Engineer

NectarCRM

Sep 2019 - Nov 2019 - 2 mos, Brazil

I worked on the development team as Front-End on the core project (NectarCRM) using the angularjs framework.

Full-stack developer

Daxplace

Apr 2018 - Sep 2019 - 1 year 5 mos, Brazil

In Daxplace I used Vue in the Front-end, and with Node.js and Laravel in the Back-end. Still, in the Daxplace Four, I had a bigger challenge, managing a team of Front-end developers. Yes, here I learned a lot about people and how they work.

Web Designer

Conexão Soluções Corporativas

Jan 20218 - Apr 2018 - 3 mos, Brazil

Development of new features to the site, backstage administration and other stuff for the product. Help to create the best UX/UI, using HTML5, CSS, JS, JQUERY, PHP and more.

Web Developer

Actuar Sistemas

Jan 2017 - Dec 2017 - 11 Mos, Brazil

In this company I worked on many fronts, from developing email marketing, setting up google adwords, creating and maintaining websites and web applications and doing customer service on social networks.

EDUCATION

Information Technology Management

SENAC - Technology University

2015 - 2018, Goiânia, Goiás, Brazil

Web Designer - Technical Course

MCTech Courses - Specialized apple

2014 - 2016, Goiânia, Goiás, Brazil



damoclesgil@gmail.com +55 62 98116-5159

About me

I'm 27 years old, I'm live in Goiânia, Goiás, Brazil, I'm a senior front-end engineer. I've been working in the area for 8 yrs.

I have a strong background in web design, user interface, and user experience. I am passionate about creating engaging, responsive, and accessible web pages.

Skills

Vue.js, Next.js, Typescript and GraphQL.

Languages

Português - Brazil (native) English (advanced)

Social

https://damoclesgil.com.br/
lim linkedin.com/in/damoclesgil
github.com/damoclesgil